imagine owning this luxury $15 million
family compound just outside of Austin
Texas this incredible property offers
three family dwellings three ponds and
over 350 Acres of Endless Possibilities
it's so awesome I can't wait to show you
let's take a
look so this estate does have three
dwellings I am standing in the main
house on the property it was built in
the 1980s so it's more traditional could
probably benefit from some modernizing
and updating but it's a really wonderful
home three bed 2 and 1/2 bath and it has
some really neat features like this wet
bar and a pool so after we finish
touring here I'll give you a view of the
entire property there's so much to show
you and I know you're going to love it
spanning over 3 50 breathtaking acres in
Nolanville Texas this extraordinary
property is just an hour outside of
Austin Texas 45 minutes south of Waco
and 25 minutes from Fort Cavazos
offering both convenience and serenity
this estate is more than just land it's
a lifestyle featuring three individual
ranches with multiple homes ponds heated
pools and a pavilion for common
Gatherings the property is perfect for
horseback riding hunting or simply
soaking in the Texas Countryside whether
you're looking for agricultural
equestrian recreational or hunting
purposes you have the option to purchase
the entire range or select individual
Properties Plus with an agricultural
exemption this is an incredible
investment this stunning 3000 ft² home
is the heart of the estate
step inside and you'll immediately
notice the natural light flooding in
from the oversized Windows um this
really illuminates the beam ceilings and
the inviting wood buring fireplace built
in 1994 the home has great bones as we
call it and with a few modern updates
new hardware fresh paint you could truly
make it your own the split floor plan
offers privacy and functionality with
two bedrooms and two baths near the
kitchen and the garage with the primary
Suite being tucked away on the opposite
side of the home the primary Suite is a
retreat of its own featuring an
expansive layout uh with a private study
and direct access to the rear patio and
pool the on Suite bathroom includes two
large closets generous counter space and
a separate tub and
shower now let's talk about this
backyard the gas pool housee house is
the perfect addition complete with a
common area kitchen and bathroom you
could really use this as a guest house
as well just imagine spending Sunny
Texas Days by the pool grilling burgers
and hot dogs and making memories with
family and friends if you're looking for
storage or workspace this home has it
all five plus garage spaces covered RV
parking and a dream workshop and the
detached
garage I am stand in the backyard of the
main home and as you can see it has the
most beautiful view your pool overlooks
your 350 acres and if you look in the
distance you can actually see a u deer
feeder there are deer all over this
property so whether you just want to be
around nature and look at some pretty
animals or you enjoy hunting the world
is your oyster here it's really
fantastic now Family compounds are very
sought after
surprisingly but very difficult to find
and so to have three homes already on
the property as well as a caraker um
home there's a little manufactured home
on the property that that was there for
the caretaker the location on top of it
is unbeatable you are right off of 190
and so everything is super secluded in
private but your location is perfect
amenities lifestyle you really have it
all with this
property just up the hill from the
primary residence is the second home a
Charming three bed two bath property
spanning about 2,000 square ft the
exterior of the home is all stone with a
detached garage and
carport sitting on a higher elevation
this home has stunning views as you
descend the property I mean seriously
wow
[Music]
now if you're wondering what this is
Outback you guess it it's a dog
run nearby there's also a grounds keeper
dwelling which is perfect for someone
helping you maintain the property or
even as an additional living space for
extended
family here is the third and final home
it actually has amazing access to i14 it
is on the Frontage Road um off of
i14 just before the entrance to the
primary residence so they own H they
each have their own little entrance to
the overall property this is another
three bed two bath home complete with
its own pool and
Cabana now inside the home is warm and
inviting featuring a cozy wood burning
fireplace separate dining and living
space and there is carpet and tile
flooring throughout
[Music]
outside you'll find another detached
garage carport and workshop these
families really love those additional
features plus a beautiful pool and the
Cabana okay this was a really really
neat feature to the property it's a
pavilion a true Gathering space to bring
all of the uh properties and individuals
individuals
together near the property's entrance
sits the Fantastic Pavilion designed for
unforgettable get togethers you can see
everything is just shaded by the
beautiful Majestic oak trees a perfect
spot for barbecues and fishing off the
Pond's dock
[Music]
okay this is one of the three ponds
behind me it is full it is beautiful it
is actually fully stocked with bass
catfish and I believe perch but really
pretty some of the really cool features
of these ponds actually is that they are
set up to where if one of them runs low
or gets too full you can turn on a valve
to replenish or move water from one Pond
to the other so I thought that was
really neat I hope that you love this
property I hope that you fell in love if
you are interested in seeing more homes
like this or would like any more
information on relocating to the central
Texas area you can find all my contact
information below I'd love to book a
zoom call with you get to know you and
see what you're looking for I'm Andrea
dudic realtor and Associate broker with
fist real estate
[Music]